Menu

Search Search Cancel

Search National Today  Submit

You are here:

* National Today Privacy Policy

National Today Privacy Policy
=============================

Effective Date: November 1, 2021

To view the Privacy Policy in effect prior to Nov 1, 2020, please [click here](https://nationaltoday.com/old-privacy-policy).

This policy discloses the privacy practices for National Today. By visiting National Today, you are accepting the practices described herein. Because National Today wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and notify you of the following:

### **1\. What information do we collect?**

The information we collect helps us ensure that our services are best designed to meet your needs. We receive and store any information that you enter on any registration page. Typically these will be registration forms for contests, surveys, or other promotions. If you are giving us information in order to participate in a survey, contest, or other promotion, your participation is completely voluntary and you, therefore, have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. If some information is required and some is optional, we will identify the required information. We collect both contact and other information.

#### **A. Contact Information**

Contact information consists of the information that we can use to contact you if, for example, you win one of the contests or promotions sponsored by National Today and/or its affiliates and partners. This consists of your name, your e-mail address, IP address, and possibly your mailing address, telephone, and facsimile number.

#### **B. Other Information**

Profile data also is collected at our site. Depending on the specific National Today products for which a user (“User”) registers, various information will be requested. We use this data to tailor the visitor’s experience through our interest-focused e-mails. By obtaining this information, we can provide our Users with specific content that we think they might be interested in, according to their preferences and interests. None of this information is required in order to receive the National Today service. The User may include only the information he or she feels comfortable including. However, the omission of certain information may limit the value of the experience for the User. As a result, the more information we have about a User, the more valuable the National Today experience will be for that User.

#### **C. Under thirteen (13)**

National Today does not intentionally collect the personal information of children under the age of thirteen (13).

### **2\. How is User information used?**

#### **A. Information that you provide**

National Today does not send unsolicited or “spam” e-mail. We use User information in a number of ways, including:

1. To send personalized, targeted information to the User in the form of e-mail messages and/or direct mail.
2. To send targeted advertising that allows us to provide our service at no or little cost to the Users.
3. To send promotions and coupons based on their interests.
4. To contact Users for feedback and surveys.
5. To monitor and improve its internal operations, as well as to ensure that it properly performs the services requested and bills properly where appropriate
6. To send Users other information about National Today and/or its products.

When you register with National Today, you may receive offers from us or our marketing partners. Our marketing partners may use this information to make offers to you in your areas of interest or other offers. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website. We may also use outside companies to execute the marketing campaigns on our behalf or on behalf of some of our marketing partners. We will share your e-mail name or other contact information that is necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purposes of providing these services.

#### **B. Automatic Information (“Cookies”)**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the User’s hard drive containing information about the User. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on National Today.com For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the User would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a User rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the User will be limited in some areas of the National Today Site. For example, the User may not be able to participate in selected Sweepstakes, Contests, or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies also can enable us to track and target the interests of our Users to enhance their experience on the National Today Site.

You can set your browser to not accept cookies. Please be aware that by doing so certain features of the National Today Site may not work. See your browser’s documentation for more information on accepting cookies.

National Today uses cookies to collect and store certain types of information when you interact with us in order to (i) access your account information (stored on our computers) and keep track of your points or credits; and (ii) learn what you like and, hence, to provide a more personalized experience for you. In the future, National Today may use cookies to enable us or a merchant to track visits to and business at its store and process the items in your shopping basket. National Today strongly encourages all of its merchants to post their privacy policies on their sites and to adhere to the same high standards as stated herein.

#### **C. Log Files**

### We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track Users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. While we collect standard Apache log files, we do not use them for any purpose other than determining page views. We also collect pages visited within our database through cookies (as discussed above). This data is connected with registration information so we can determine site usage and for marketing research. Except in the case of domain name registrations, IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  

### **3\. Does National Today share information it collects?**

#### **A. Registration Information**

As part of the registration process, we often offer you the option to take advantage of one or more offers from our partners. Those offers are optional and you do not have to sign-up for any offers in order to participate in the main promotional offer (although you may need to check or uncheck certain boxes to do so). If you do choose to sign-up for an offer, we will share information about you with those selected partners from whom you have chosen to receive information. All offers have Terms and Conditions links that we encourage you to read.

When you register with National Today, you can elect to sign up with some of our marketing partners so they may contact you with their special offers. Our marketing partners wishing to contact you either give their e-mail message to us and we deliver it to you, or with your prior permission, we provide your contact information to them so they can deliver messages directly to you. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website. We may share this information with a third-party advertising company in order to market more effectively to you.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., outsourced e-mail delivery companies). They have access to the User information to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

#### **B. Referral Program**

As part of some of our referral programs, we request contact information (like the name and e-mail address) of visitors’ friends and family whom they think would like to receive a National Today service. The persons referred to us will receive sample National Today e-mails, but do not become subscribers until they confirm their interest in the service. National Today stores this information for the sole purpose of sending emails regarding National Today services. The person referred also can unsubscribe at any time; see “What Choices Do I Have,” below.

#### **C. Protection of National Today and Others**

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Except as otherwise stated in this policy, it is against our policy to provide any customer information to third parties without the customer’s prior permission. As part of our business, however, we also provide links to third-party sites. We encourage all of our merchants to post their privacy policies on their sites and to adhere to the same high standard as is stated here. We, however, disclaim any responsibility for the actions of these third parties. AS A RESULT, WE ENCOURAGE OUR USERS TO READ THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE LINKED SITES, BECAUSE THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES MAY DIFFER FROM OURS.

#### **D. Links To Other Sites**

We may release User or account information as is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of National Today, its subsidiaries, affiliates or partners, our Users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

### **4\. What Choices do I have?**

#### **A. Choices In Disclosing Information**

Because we want our Users to feel completely comfortable using the National Today services, we provide you with various opportunities to control how the information you provide to us will be used by us. We request information from our customers’ registration, as well as via surveys or contests, or other promotions. Your participation in these activities is completely voluntary and you, therefore, have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Nevertheless, certain basic information is required in order to register as a User. Information requested may include contact information and demographic information. You also may choose whether or not to get e-mails from National Today and whether or not to accept special offers from our partners. If you choose not to receive e-mails from National Today we will not send you e-mails, although it may take a short time to remove your name from our database.  

Please note once an account is created, we may send you a confirmation e-mail acknowledging your new account to the address that you supplied us. This e-mail will give you the option to unsubscribe your account, in case you change your mind or in case you were not the one who created it in the first place. You should keep the confirmation e-mail, as it will also contain information that will help you in case you run into problems accessing our services.

#### **B. Opting Out**

To remove your User information from our mailing list(s) so as not to receive future communications from us or to no longer receive our service, please send an email to webmaster@nationaltoday.com. If you have submitted personal information under more than one e-mail account, you must make this request from each account that you have used. National Today will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete records from our mailing list when we receive requests to do so. Please allow up to 48 hours to be completely removed from our database. If we decide to change this privacy statement, we will post those changes on this Web site so our Users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

### **5\. How secure is my information?**

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of that information. In addition, certain of the National Today Sites encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to it (e.g., credit card numbers, account passwords) in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity. Financial information is stored in a secure location that is accessible only by designated staff and used only for the purposes for which you provide the information.

While we strive to protect your personal information, National Today cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In addition, National Today and third party Internet sites and services accessible through National Today or parties whom we inform you are collecting data in connection with contests, games, promotions, etc., have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. National Today has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

### **6\. ​​Users in the State of California only**

If you live in California, you also have certain rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) to request certain information from certain businesses that collect that information from and about you. This California Privacy Policy contains disclosures required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and applies only to “personal information” that is subject to that law. Below are the CCPA rights that you may exercise regarding your personal information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations.

#### **The right to be informed.** You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your information and your rights. This is why we’re providing you with the information in this Privacy Policy.

**The right of access.** You have the right to obtain access to the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you, the business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information, the categories of third parties with whom we have shared your personal information, and the business or commercial purpose for selling your personal information, if applicable. This is so you’re aware and can check that we’re using your information in accordance with data protection law.

**The right to delete.** You have the right to request we delete the personal information we have collected from you. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities. 

**The right to withdraw consent.** If you have given your consent to anything we do with your personal data, such as receiving direct marketing, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time (although if you do so, it does not mean that anything we have done with your personal data with your consent up to that point is unlawful). You can withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal information at any time.

**Do Not Sell My Personal Information.** You have the right to request that we do not sell your personal data to third parties. In order to opt out of the sale of personal data to third parties, please contact us using the information provided in the Contact Us section below.

The **right not to receive discriminatory treatment** for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.

We may charge a reasonable fee to cover our administrative costs of providing the information for baseless or excessive/repeated requests, or further copies of the same information. Alternatively, we may be entitled to refuse to act on the request.  Please consider your request before submitting it. We will respond as soon as we can – generally within thirty (30) days from when we receive your request. To send us a request please refer to the contact information listed below.

### **Using an Authorized Agent to Submit a Request**

You may designate an authorized agent to make a CCPA request on your behalf by writing to us at the contact information provided below. To the extent we are unable to verify your identity when you make the designation request, we may request additional information from you. Note, if designating an entity to act on your behalf, the CCPA requires that such entity must be registered with the California Secretary of State.

If you reside in California you may request certain details about our disclosure of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make a request for this information, please reach out to us at the contact information listed below.

**How to Submit a Request**

To exercise your California consumer rights to request, know or delete, please contact us at team@nationaltoday.com with the subject line “CCPA Request,” and the relevant request identified in the body of the email.

### **7\. Contact Us**

Please contact us by email at [team@nationaltoday.com](mailto:team@nationaltoday.com) or by mail at 719 Clementina St. B San Francisco, CA 94103 if you have any questions about our privacy policy or to exercise your rights hereunder.

**Additional Disclosures under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018**
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| #### **Personal Information** | #### **Source(s) of Collection** | #### **Purpose for Collection** | #### **Shared with Third Parties** |
| Identifiers such as a real name, alias, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, or other similar identifiers | * User Registration<br>* Surveys | * Performance of Services | * Cloud Storage Providers<br>* Other third parties only with your consent |
| Geolocation Data | We do not collect or share this information | We do not collect or share this information. | We do not collect or share this information. |
| Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law such as gender and date of birth. | * User Registration | * Auditing<br>* Content Personalization | * Cloud Storage Providers<br>* Other third parties only with your consent |
| Internet or other similar network activity such as browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our website, systems, and advertisements. | * Website cookies<br>* Web Beacons | * Performance of Services<br>* Auditing<br>* Activities to maintain quality and safety of Services | * Cloud Storage Providers<br>* Other third parties only with your consent |
| Professional or employment-related information | User Registration | Content Personalization | * Cloud Storage Providers<br>* Other third parties only with your consent |
| Education Information | We do not collect or share this information. | We do not collect or share this information. | We do not collect or share this information. |
| Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this table to create a profile about a User reflecting such User’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | Web Beacons | * Performance of Services<br>* Activities to maintain quality and safety of Services | * Cloud Storage Providers<br>* Other third parties only with your consent |

Pin

105 Shares

Pin

105 Shares

* 6,172 Days celebrated
* 18,516 Ways to celebrate
* 10,000,000+ Happy users

### About us

### Resources

### Contact Us

### Our Services

### Months

### Upcoming

### All Months

### Gifts

### Blog

### Shopping Reviews

### Gift Guides

### Popular Holidays

### About National Today

We keep track of fun holidays and special moments on the cultural calendar — giving you exciting activities, deals, local events, brand promotions, and other exciting ways to celebrate.

### Follow us on

Copyright © 2017–2024 by National Today. [Privacy policy](https://nationaltoday.com/privacy-policy/)
